<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LectureMaterial_04_MovingBetweenActivities</string>
    <string name="script_scene_01">It was a cold bur-season day. A student walks onto a computer with a cup of coffee in hand. She takes a sip of the warm brew. Her breath fogs as she exhales. She thinks to herself how can she finish the project at such short notice. The managers barely give her enough time. A soft sigh leaves her lips. A small chukle, as if losing hope. The coffee is barely keeping her awake. Two days of no sleep causes her head to spin. She looks to her left and sees a soft bed. Tempting and soft, it calls to her like a siren calling sailors.</string>
    <string name="script_scene_01_choice_1">Go to sleep</string>
    <string name="script_scene_01_choice_2">Push on with the project</string>
    <string name="script_scene_02">She puts her hand on her head. She can\'t concentrate. She thinks to herself a power-nap should do the trick. She assures herself she will finish the project. She rests her head on the pillow and loses herself to a world of dreams within seconds. She drifts slowly into a peaceful calm when suddenly her phone rings. Her partner is asking for her part. Sadly, she picked a bad ringtone of a bomb exploding. Adrenaline fills her body jolting her awake. A full 3 hours have passed and she works to finish her task. She barely finishes but completes the project. All is well.</string>
    <string name="script_scene_03">She takes a sip of her coffee and slaps her cheeks firmly. She has a job to do. The feeling of duty rejuvenates her body. She powers on through with all the strength in her mind. Running on fumes. desperate! But with this act, she surpasses her body forcing her vessel to be driven by her will. Hours pass then her partner messages her checking on her progress. With pride, she passes her work that is complete and well made. She requests to her friend if she can take the rest of the day off. With a gentle response, she smiles as she sees the ok. Looking at the screen of her from with her hed on the pillow, she buries the phone under the blanket and takes a much deserved rest. All is well.</string>
    <string name="script_scene_04">The next day, the girl proudly comes to her school. Proud of her accomplishment and ready to face whatever grade may befall onto her. She walks up the steps and sees her partner. She walks up to him and exclaims:</string>
    <string name="script_04_scene_commend_1">You know, you would make a great alarm clock!</string>
    <string name="script_04_scene_commend_2">That was a great nights sleep!</string>
</resources>